Hey S. Hello Nimrod and Nimrod. How are
you?
We're good. We're good. Thank you. Doing
well. Awesome. Awesome. I'll do a very
very brief intro and then we can kind of
jump straight in. So we have Nimrod
Core. Nimrod. Nimrod Core. Would you
mind putting your hand up? Nimrod.
Nimrod on the left is Nimrod Core.
Nimrod's a software engineer. I was I
was loved hearing that you're the number
one contributor to Czechov, the very
popular IA security tool, which is
awesome. Um, awesome to hear. And and uh
we also have Nimrodhouser. Nimrod, how
are you? Great. Nimro on the right
there. Nimrod describes himself as a
serial first employee in the startup
space. I really love that. And Nimrod,
you bridge that gap between software
development and data engineering as
well, right? Yeah. Awesome. Awesome.
Well, a big big welcome to you both. And
what I'm going to do is I'm going to put
your uh slides up on screen now and a
big thank you to Baz for also being a
kind partner of this uh of this
conference and I'll hand over to uh to
you both. So enjoy the session. Thank
you. Thank you for having us, Simon. Uh
welcome everybody. Uh today we're going
to talk a little bit about building a
retrievable Kobe memory model. There's
lots of big words in there. So let's uh
uh start taking this apart uh one by
one. Uh so a little bit about us. As
Simon said, I'm uh the co-founder CTO of
Baz. I've been building backend stuff on
AWS for uh more than 10 years. I also do
some open source projects. Check over
ifastic. They're awesome. Use them if
you need to. They're uh highly
recommended. Uh and I'm not biased at
all. Alongside me is another numero. I'm
going to call him Hower. Uh he's our
first employee. He's a serial uh
founding employee as Simon said and also
he really runs the entire field between
backend engineering, data engineering,
data science, um dashboards, uh and
anything else you might need. Uh he's
the guy for it. Uh let's jump in. So
what are we going to talk about? First
of all, we're going to talk a little bit
about what we do at Baz. Uh because it
helps us present the main challenge that
we need to break up here, which is the
uh codebased memory. Uh the second thing
we'll talk about is how context is king
and how it meets the software
development and then we'll actually get
to the juicy stuff and talk about how we
tried failed and then succeeded we think
uh building retrievable memory. Um so
let's uh let's get started. What is
Buzz? Buzz is an AI powered code review
platform. What that means is we've built
a number of agents that do lots of
things that help review code, right? So,
it's a state-of-the-art code code
reviewing agent. Um, it does PR
summaries, uh, which summarizes the
changes. It does review comments to
identify, uh, what the change has done
and maybe it's up to some bad stuff,
including custom principles. So, trying
to identify what works best on your
codebase. It does code graphs which
analyze the diff in a visual manner to
help you understand what change and what
affects what or what is the chain of
events that is going to happen. And of
course, we have our own uh small AI
assistant which will helpfully assist in
anything you need to do around pull
request and code review. Now, this all
sounds amazing, right? We have a
state-of-the-art code reviewing agent.
It does all these things. What's the
problem?
Well, I'm glad you asked, Nimrod. So, we
built our our platform, our reviewer,
and everything seemed to be working
amazing. It did everything it was
supposed to do, and results were were
good. But as we kind of got a feeling
for our own product and we were kind of
dog fooding our own stuff, something
felt a little bit missing and we just we
try we took it took us some time to
understand what it was until we thought
we finally had it. The main feedback we
got and our own feeling was that our
reviewer was a bit too robotic. It felt
like it kind of lacked an understanding.
it understood what was happening but it
kind of didn't understand why where how
is this the best way to do this thing
and I think this uh I have an example
here that kind kind of exemplifies this
so this is a PR description that we've
generated a while back before we made
some upgrades and we can kind of take a
quick look it says you know you change
this class you change a method the input
change the structure is a little a
little bit different everything it says
is correct that really happened but it's
kind of like a dry reiteration
regurgitation of just what happened.
There's no I I guess the the magic word
is context. So that was the thing that
was missing and we thought that's what
what's required for that you know that
next step that X factor and in these
cases people often say that context is
king. Apparently it is a saying and this
I have here something that exemplifies
this. It's this nice little picture. you
you see the same symbol twice, but one
time you understand that it's a B and
the other time it's a number. It's 13.
And the only reason you know this is
because of the surrounding stuff,
because of the context. Now, this is
important, but you might ask yourself,
okay, I get it, but how does context
actually come into play when you're
doing pull requests? What's the
connection? Great question, Hower. Um so
when we look at the developer mindset
when he uh approaches code review uh we
split the mindset into three parts. The
first and most basic part is you need to
understand code right if you want to
review code obviously uh but you also
when you try to step up your review game
you need to understand where this change
fits within the system right so I have
maybe multiple components multiple apps
multiple services I changed something
what's
going to change for a code review is to
understand what will be the user impact
right I changed this function it means
this service or services will need to be
updated And that means that new
functionality will be exposed, old
functionality will be removed. What what
exactly happens? So when we're trying to
do this with AI, what we decided to do
is uh approach each uh of these levels
differently for this uh most simple
level. The
diff give the diff with slightly better
formatting. But then when we look at the
holistic perspective, you need to add
more context which is beyond the scope
of the diff that actually changed and
when we talk about the uh uh business
impact we also link to the uh ticketing
service. So it's a Jira linear whatever
you're using uh and for this talk or
what we saw as the main impact here it
was the flow context. So what is flow
context or codebased memory? What we
wanted to do is we wanted to create a
summary that defines what this piece of
code does uh in general terms pretty uh
uh holistic what it does in total
because when we use that to review code
to summarize code to do all the things
that I listed before we'll just do it
better because we know what we're
working on. So let's say XYZ is a
parameter that you created in the PR,
but it's also the name of your company.
So it's not a typo. It's not a mistake.
It makes sense to name that parameter by
that name. Uh I have an example here of
a flow context. It's a pretty long and
uh boring paragraph, but what you can
see if you read a few words there is
that it's very specific to what a
specific um module or a specific part of
the code that we have does. uh it's
actually a real part of our codebase. It
analyzes languages uh and we'll talk
more about it later.
Okay. So, we understand what we want to
achieve. We want to at the end of the
day, we're trying to generate this
paragraph that gives me a description of
what this area of code does. It's worth
mentioning that we do have a lot of
other prompts in the system because we
do a lot of things and and we might have
one prompt that we send out for to an
LLM to summarize the PR and another
prompt um in order to actually do the
code review. So what we want to do now
is want to generate that paragraph that
just showed so that we can inject that
into all the other prompts to make our
uh our system better. as a first step as
we start our journey now towards
generating this. I can't stress how
important this is to do a le the leanest
P you can and it's it means it's going
to be manual. We just took our prompts
and we ran them and we saw the output.
For example, a a PR summary. Then we
manually wrote the flow context and we
added that to our prompt. We ran it
again and we wanted to see if there's a
difference. It is kind of exemplified in
this meme. Great show. Amazing. And
you'd be surprised by by the number of
times that we we thought we added
context, but the result the PR summary
at the end was exactly the same. We're
the same image. And so and so this
really this process really not only did
it prove the value, but it also gave us
a good understanding of what it is we're
trying to achieve. Like this paragraph
should be long, short, technical, high
level, handwavy, full of examples. So
that's super super super important. Once
we understood there's value in it, we
were free to actually start automating
it. So, okay. So, now we understand our
task. Our task is to sprinkle context to
make the LLM better. But what does that
mean? It means that we take whatever is
at our disposal, code snippets, diffs,
other stuff that we'll talk about, and
we have all this data and we need to
find the best way to crunch it in a way
that the LLM
understands. And at this point, you
might ask yourself, well, but why is
this? Yeah, why is this hard? I mean,
why can't I just take the naive
approach, the straightforward one where
I take the entire repository and just
feed the entire raw co raw code into the
LLM and say, you know, summarize this.
Why not? Why not? Well, uh there are a
few problems with it. First of all, it's
expensive and it is slow. These models
are very notorious for being very very
very slow and feeding so much so many
tokens in is going to be problematic and
that translates to being just completely
unscalable. Moving on. So a lot of
research has been done around what we
call the lost in the middle problem or
context fatigue. And research shows that
uh the long the longer the prompt gets,
LLMs can start to forget, get confused,
ignore part of the instructions, and so
forth. Uh you can look at the graph that
really shows this clearly. Uh I don't
think there are there are many more
efficient ways to make your prompt way
too long than just feeding it excessive
amounts of code. So might not be the
best solution there. Uh also context
windows. Yes, there are models who
support ginormous context windows
nowadays, but they're few and far
between. Uh, having context windows so
large really limits your freedom in
choosing models and leaves you kind of
only with the slowest ones, most
expensive ones and so forth. So again,
big disadvantage. And lastly, code
changes and it changes a lot. And if you
and that's where you kind of meet your
business requirements because if you say
you know product comes and says you need
to run this at least once a day if not
you know if not at higher frequency um
then that's going to be a problem if the
process really is really heavy expensive
and so on and so forth. Okay at this
point it is worth mentioning there are
some honorable mentions. There are very
famous uh projects that do exactly this
thing. They take entire repositories and
they just you know they summarize them.
On the right we can see get in ingest.
On the left we can see deep deep wiki
and we encourage you to go and check
them out but if you do you might see
that often times the data is a bit
stale. It's usually not up to date and
probably because of the reasons we just
listed. And so we understood at that
point you know we'll just have to do it
ourselves. Yep. Amazing. But before we
do, let's do a quick uh lingo break.
We're going to throw some terms around.
I just want to stop uh focus on two. Uh
we will throw the word module a lot. And
by that we just mean everything that
comes all the code that's managed by a
single uh kind of package manager.
Everything under the same uh package
JSON, pip files, rust crates, Maven pom
files, these are modules or subm
modules. And the other thing application
flow. Application flow is also a term we
throw around. It's an illdefined hazy
term for everything that just kind of
makes sense as a sequence of logical
steps in the system. Think anything
behind an endpoint, behind a queue, a
batch process, everything that just
makes sense as an application flow. I
know it's
circular. All right. So, we can come
back uh to our journey. Our journey is
how do we take an entire module and we
squeeze that into an LLM. So first of
all uh at our at Buzz we usually use
modules. Why modules? Well we find it's
kind of a sweet spot. It's not as big as
repositories. Repositories sometimes
have too many things going on, too many
responsibilities. Modules are often kind
of better uh structured. uh if they if
they are if they're structured uh if if
we're not talking about like a poly repo
project where a module might equal a
repository but often times it helps all
the monor repo guys will thank us and uh
we wanted to going in we really wanted
to leverage batch processing and
premputation if we could so our first
attempts uh were trying to use that and
spoiler alert uh we kind of went another
direction that we'll talk about that. So
we started out trying to uh summarize
entire modules and towards the end we
took a different path. I'll talk about
that uh going forward. I'll just say if
you're choosing not to uh summarize
entire modules and you're going with
individual files, it's important to
remember that sometimes documents that
are not in a PR are important if you
want to understand an application flow.
And I have a a very small example here.
Let's say I have document A that imports
document B that imports document C.
Document A and C might be part of the
PR. If you're trying to understand the
application flow, how everything's
connected, you you're going to want to
include document B as well. We'll see
that going
in. All right. So, what did we try? How
did we try to, you know, squeeze all
that data into the LLM? The first
approach we tried was leveraging
something called TF. For those who for
those people who are not NLP nerds,
natural language processing, uh TF is a
really cool technique. It stands for
term frequency and inverse document
frequency. In these NLP uh methodologies
usually have a bunch of documents, a
bunch of text items and they this pool
of text documents they create something
called they you know they compose
something called a corpus and in our
example every module was a corpus. So we
had a lot of modules uh that we kind of
uh processed to analyzed together and in
each module we analyzed each and every
word and we looked for two things the TF
and the IDF. So the TF means we look at
each word and we're trying to see is it
a common word. When I said that we're
looking at words in a module we're
usually in our use case we're looking at
class names method names. So I can look
at the method name like get value or get
item and the TF might be really high. it
might appear a lot and I can say, "Wow,
that's a really common word. It's
probably really really really
interesting. It's really important, but
then I look at other modules out in the
wild. I compare it and I say, "Oh, it's
really popular everywhere." So, it's
it's just a common it's just a common
term. And so, the uniqueness of it kind
of drops. The TF gives me gives me a TF
score. It's essentially a uniqueness
score. So, if it's a very common word in
the wild, it's less unique. But let's
take a look at something from our
domain. Let's say I see a method name
called analyze diff. And that might be a
really common phrase, but it's not as
common in other modules. It'll only
appear in modules doing, you know, a
stuff and uh static code analysis. And
so that will get a higher TF score. What
we uh what we used this technique for
was to zero in on the important
documents, the unique documents, and the
unique methods and classes. And by zero
zeroing in on the proprietary stuff, we
thought we'd have a good chance at
understanding what the module does and
summarizing the important stuff.
Exactly. So we generated something that
looks like this. You know, all the
important files, all the important
methods, uh, kind of ranked by by
uniqueness. And that's what we actually
fed the LLM. We said, "Hey, here's a
module. This is kind of what it does.
Um, here here's a list of methods. Can
you tell me what it does?" And it worked
really
well.
But reality uh came knocking and we
realized that not everything is the sexy
proprietary stuff. We also have our
run-of-the-mill web servers, Q handlers,
event handlers, all that all that kind
of common stuff. And when it's less
unique, that's where TF started having
murky results. So as you started
evaluating that stuff, we we realized
that we have to go another way and
evaluation by the way is a is an
important point. We will get to that.
It's a huge part of it. Did you see this
right from the first example or did you
need to look through multiple modules to
actually get a feel on this? That's
another amazing question. Thanks.
And so when we started out, people
sometimes like they have their like an
example that they like the repo that
they usually work on and like they
analyze that again and again and again
and and running and doing iterations on
the same on the same example has its
benefits because you kind of get a
feeling for it and you get like your own
gut feeling and a benchmark. But that's
also a that's also a trap because
sometimes you will get good results on
one example and when we move to other
repositories, we started analyzing our
front end and our BFF of the back end
for front end repo and that's when
things just fell apart. These were the
the repositories that had the more
generic stuff and suddenly it didn't
work. So that's super super important
and thanks for bringing that up. So next
um great. So this is a great setup to
talk about about something else that
we've built alongside uh the module
memory and that's the connection graph.
when we look at analyzing uh modules
specifically a module has a a lot of
files that interact with each other
directly right it's not an external
input that goes through a different uh
package uh so what we do is we scan all
the files using tricitter it's an
amazing open source that analyzes I
think 138 different languages to find
the different uh I would say building
blocks per language because some
languages have classes and some have
strs some have functions and some have
receiver functions go Um so we try to uh
grab all the important uh pieces or
blocks we call them code elements and
then we need to classify them. So we
have imports, we have functions,
classes, enums, invocations, all of that
stuff. And then the last step we try to
make to do is resolve the relationships
between them. Why? Because when you
change a function, I want to know who
uses that function. Right? If I'm
modifying a a call to a function, I want
to see what it what its body looks like.
So, we try to resolve the uh uh all of
the relationships when we understand
what we're reviewing. But this also
matches with this uh module memory. What
we thought we would do is instead of
using TF, let's just grab all of the
names of all of the methods and classes
in a module, right? We just put them in
a list and send them to the LLM. What's
the problem? So obviously that is still
too much data. It's very similar to
sending the entire code. I mean it's
still less but it's still a lot and it
explodes. Um you see here a picture of a
connection graph. That's how a
connection graph looks on one of our
modules. Uh again one of our modules uh
graphs tend to be really hard to read
very fast. And so we understood we have
to make this smaller. uh what we decided
to try out was Luvine. Luvine is an
algorithm to identify strongly connected
components within a graph. So let's say
you have a a main pie and it uh imports
a few files and these files each one of
them is completely separate from the
other and it has a whole module and uh
service and DB and controller and
whatever. So each one of those would be
a strongly uh strongly connected
component. And what we wanted to do is
find a representative the most important
or unique uh file within each sec and
take only the elements from that. So
take only the class names the functions
from that representative file and well
it solved the problem of the size right
it can still be pre premputed it it
fixes the TF uh in the wild issue. we
get actually everything we need. But
then we ran into the issue with the
thing with summary is by definition it
drops the less important stuff. Right?
If I ask to summarize a document, there
might be things that just won't make it
into the summary. And the problem we
faced is we look at some PRs and we saw
that those PRs change a specific point
in this module and it might be the
central point and it might be a
secondary point. it might be a new
feature that is not within the summary
and then nothing is relevant at all. Uh
so what we understood is the problem is
different. We don't need to summarize
the entire module because it just
doesn't work.
Yeah. So what did we do? So we
understood that the entire module is
going to be a problem in some modules
that are more kind of cluttered and just
have a lot of things going on. And it's
interesting because Luvine worked
amazingly well from a technical
standpoint or a data science standpoint.
It did exactly what it was it was meant
to do. It's just that the the problem we
were asking just wasn't the correct one.
We understood that we have to be laser
focused. We we want at the end of the
day we need to ask ourselves again what
is our goal and we want to create a
summary not for the sake of creating a
module summary but we want to give
context to a specific PR that we're
going to analyze and so what we decided
is that we're going to ask the LLM to
summarize the module as if the only
thing that the module is doing is what
the PR is concerned with for example our
BFF uh module like I said it's super
cluttered it does you know It has the
our our AI chatbot and it does event
handling and queue handling and and
endpoints web service uh and a lot of
other notification center and a lot of
other things. And we said okay let's say
I have a PR that deals within the you
know the notification center feature. So
I'm going to ask the LLM to summarize
the module is if the only thing the
module is doing is notification center.
That way I can make sure that the
important stuff make it into the summary
in so we understood that we're not going
to uh analyze the modules like entire
modules modules in their in their
entirety and each each uh attempt is
going to be slightly different which
means we can't really do premp
computation at least not in the way that
we did it before. So, we're going to be
like custom, right? And uh and so what
we did is that we look in every PR, we
look at the documents in the PR and we
said before when we did the spoiler
alert that sometimes you have documents
in the PR, but if you're trying to
understand that the the application
flow, sometimes you will have documents
that are not in the PR, right, that are
very heavily connected and so and so
they're important. So, we did a little
bit of graph theory magic and we looked
for the best way to find these things.
And here in the graph you can see an
example where we have a PR and the nodes
are documents. The red nodes symbolize
the documents that are in the PR. The
blue nodes are documents that are not in
the PR but they are connected. They're
very very related. And so we included
those as well. And that's pretty much
how we approach this. So we leverage the
connection graph and before to what
extend the context. Exactly. And then
those are the files from which we take
uh you know their content and we send
that to the LLM. I see.
So the the the wins here are that we're
laser focused as before and when we
looked at the results it made the impact
that we were looking for. It's the the
you know the summaries the the the
reviews everything was spoton. So we
knew that that was it. The problem is
that it's not precomputed um in its
entirety like we wanted. There is though
still a retrievable element to it
because creating graphs for the entire
module is heavy. That is something we do
um kind of in a precomputed manner. We
create the horrible uh import graph that
we saw in the unreadable one in your
slide the unreadable one. And what we do
on the fly is we just understand which
parts of it we need to take uh and
analyze uh and send to the LLM kind of
that we do on the fly. So it's kind of a
really cool hybrid approach. And then
for the files that we selected, what do
you send to the what is the actual
payload per file? So actually it's very
similar to what we did in the TF. We
take all we actually take all the method
names and all the class names and we
send that and you know we played with it
in order to see what works. that that
works and that is certainly enough uh
for the LLM to tell you what the module
is doing which is good news because we
actually discovered that we don't need
to send the the raw code in its
entirety. We can send much fewer tokens
and we still get what we need. Cool. So
it works, right? That's it. We're done.
Uh not quite because I still want to
take like a minute to just kind of
briefly mention evaluation. Yeah, this
is you know this is important. This is a
crucial part, an integral part of every
data science, ML, AI, what project,
what, whatever name you want to give it.
Uh, super important. And this problem in
particular was interesting because you
could say that it's kind of a soft
problem. I mean, in our use case, if you
want to do something like a PR summary,
you're going to have the summary either
way, but it can be a good summary or it
can be a not so good summary. And it's
very it's really about style, wording,
you know, that kind of thing. We started
out saying that it felt too robotic. How
do you measure that? Yeah. You know, and
so you start by eyeballing it and
getting a feeling for it. And that that
is not being lazy. That is just a quick
a way to iterate quickly. But once you
start getting into the path and you
start automating stuff, it's crucial
that you build a framework uh for
benchmarking.
And uh and you know, one of the most
common ways is using LLM as a judge. I
want to uh mention two cool approaches
that you can uh use to build something
like that even in our soft use case.
One, you just ask the LLM if the end
result seems good. So you give it the
summary in our example and you give it
the flow context and you ask it, hey, do
you think uh this was generating using
was the the the final summary uh
referencing this context? And you just
count you give it a lot of examples. You
ask it a lot of times and just count the
number of times it says yes, right? And
that's your benchmark. And then you run
it every time. You make changes to make
sure there are no regressions and things
of that nature. I think a slightly
cooler approach is that you create two
summaries kind of like the meme we
showed before from the with Pam from the
office without with context and without
context and you ask which do you think
is better and uh and you count the
number of times that the that the
description with that was made with
context was better. Now it becomes part
of your DNA of your culture because you
have this benchmark and the benchmark
obviously has a pool of examples that
you kind of curate and you you kind of
collect along the way and you know as we
work in our day-to-day thing uh people
say oh that's a nice example let's add
it to the curated list. So it's really
really nice and everybody's kind of in
on it. Um two things one I think the
evaluation is what helped us move stuff
into production at a much higher
confidence. Uh, but I do have one
question for you. LLM is a judge. Does
it matter which LLM? Oh, that's that's
cool. Pro tip. Um, just make sure you're
using a different model. Don't ask, you
know, clots on it to judge clots on it.
It's actually pretty pretty cool because
you're asking like, you know, entropic
to judge OpenAI, the other way around.
Usually that gives you better results
because the models can be biased towards
their own generated output. My god,
they're like people. Yes. part last
slide. Uh quick takeaways from our
journey. I think we mentioned everything
as we went along, but let's just run
through them. First of all, don't rush
to build. Hands to keyboard is super
tempting. But as we showed before, take
your the necessary time to understand
what you want to build, how it needs to
look, does it make an impact? Do that
stuff before running, you know, uh full
steam ahead. Be open to change. We
wanted we wanted to analyze entire
modules. we wanted to do premputation.
Uh you know both things kind of didn't
work out and it's fine. You just need to
adapt as you learn more information.
Don't fall in love with a single
example. As we saw the number of times I
was ready to sign in on something saying
this works and then we tried another
repo and things completely fall apart is
just too damn high. And evaluation
evaluate evaluate evaluate super super
important. That is your way of knowing
that you're still on track, that you
still have high quality, that you're not
deteriorating. I think these are the
main points. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you.
Awesome. And thank you very much. That
was a really really interesting session.
We had a number of questions in the
background that I kind of put in a list
as well. So uh let me uh let me quickly
remove that from screen so we can see
all better. We have a number of
questions. Let's see which one we should
pick first.
Um uh actually an interesting one maybe
kind of like from a from from the from
the fact that I guess you know I in
terms of in terms of comparisons with
other tools. Uh what would you say I
guess things like sorcery and the like
uh and I think there was another one
that was mentioned uh I think graphite
is a is another one.
Um how would you say it compares? What
are the what are the advantages with
bats? So I would say uh first of all I
love the other competitors in this field
and uh I as like two years ago I never
thought AI would review my code and now
I'm having a hard time living without
it. Um I would say that where Baz
differentiates from all the rest is all
of the a work that I kind of hinted at
when we talked about solution number
two. So all of the a stuff and all of
the engine that we built out to actually
understand the language, find the things
that are important, find the links and
relationships between them. Uh and then
pass that into the LLM. It's kind of a
you need to move into the space of
objects and then back into the space of
text to actually have the LM understand
what you're saying because uh when we
sent out graphs, it just hallucinated.
Um, so you really have to turn it into
text. And that's kind of the amazing
thing where when you start to talk to it
like you talk to other developers in
objects and functions and classes and
not in lines and text, it understands
better and that's what our entire system
is built on. Awesome. Awesome. Uh, we
have a another couple. Um first of all
I'll ask um we just recently you were
talking about the kind of um you know
maybe a little bit
about the the judging and things like
that. Um here's a question in around can
current LLM reason meaningfully over
large modules. Um so I guess even before
we get to that stage uh how does it how
does the size of the module matter
because I guess with huge amounts of
context we've seen that degradation
across all models before we even get
anywhere close to the maximum context
windows of of of uh models. H how does
it deal with larger larger amounts of
code bases to to look through?
Uh great question.
So models models v vary and it varies by
module it varies by by vendor. We talked
about the loss in the middle problem and
and even that problem behaves
differently between different vendors.
For example, you know uh we see that
entropic models give more more attention
to things at the end of the prompt. Open
AI models give more attention to things
at the beginning of the prompt. So
everything everything uh kind of works
slightly differently. And we mentioned
that the modules are sometimes biased
towards their own output because it's
what they know. It's what they've been
trained on and therefore, you know, it
seems more familiar.
Um, and so and so
um and so it's so it's more it's there's
a lot of trial and error that goes into
it um to see what works and what
doesn't. I will say that there aren't a
lot of use cases where we put in a ton
of code because at the end of the day
we're usually not uh you know we're
that's the also the whole point of the
talk. We're trying not to uh input the
the entire codebase. We're trying to to
minimize to to aggregate to to filter
and so that I think is one of the thing
things that makes this uh work. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll say that when we tried out uh
different stuff uh as the as the context
gets longer, the LLM starts uh just
forgetting stuff that you said. Um so
not replying the structure you asked or
just uh forgetting some kind of I love
the do not do blah blah blah uh uh
instructions and it just forgets them
and does it anyway. Uh and those are the
things that happen when the context gets
too large. Yeah. Okay. Awesome. Uh we're
about a minute and a half over, but
because I'm a terrible host, I'm gonna
ask one more question. I think it'll be
a quick one. Um so a couple of
questions. One from in fact similar
questions. One, uh Richard Doc uh from
uh from Discord asks, "Is there any
example code for the TDF approach?" You
remember two days? So
I I think we deleted that code actually.
And uh I I have I think it's called a
pet peeve like uh where I do a lot of
too many things in SQL. TF was like a
600 line SQL queries that I don't think
anybody wants. Um but but there there I
mean TF at the end of the day is like a
I don't you know it's an equation or a
formula but it's really simple. I mean
it's a you can search like TF in
Wikipedia and you can see the
calculation. It's super simple. uh once
you understand like the gist of it,
implementation is really
straightforward.
Awesome. Cool. Cool. Cool. Well, a
massive thank you uh to Nimrod and
Nimrod for all of your insights and and
and and uh and wishing Baz all the best
as well and thank you very much for
supporting two years in a row. So, very
very much appreciate that. Thank you.
Bye, Simon.